mmorpg-life.com 2018-12-21

# MMORPG Life » Privacy PolicyMMORPG Life

At Mmorpg-Life.com we recognize that privacy is important. This policy describes the ways we collect and use your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the services and websites offered by Mmorpg-Life.com. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available at the top or at the bottom of all of our pages.

  1. **How we collect information about you**  
The only information we collect are related to site contributors. If you write a comment or if you register as a site contributor, we collect the following types of information from you:  
– Email address you can access  
– IP addressAny other information collected would be provided entirely at your choice.
  2. **How we use the personal information we collect:**  
We do not share any of this information with outside parties.
  3. **How you can access or change your personal information**  
You can review and edit your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing your profile.
  4. **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
